see-hub.tk 2016-01-05

# Privacy Policy OF SeeHub

Privacy Policy:

About SeeHub

www.seehub.tk ("SeeHub") is a website owned and operated by Ilyesoft Studio ("we", "our", "us"). The terms ("You", "Visitor", "user", "your") mean you and every one who visited any page in www.seehub.tk and/or use the search form. 

The SeeHub web search service is powered by Google Custom Search ("Google"). You should read Google's privacy policy at: <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

The privacy of our visitors to www.seehub.tk is important to us. And we are strongly committed to protecting your privacy while interacting with SeeHub.

Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying experience while allowing you to control your privacy and to give you a means to voice any questions or concerns you may have.

Almost all our results pages are hosted by google.com ("Google"), every time you search with our search forms ( in our home page or any other page, including forms in results pages) we will redirect you to google website, or show you search results from Google Engine instead. See [google Privacy Policy ](http://www.google.com/privacy.html) .

Collection and use of your information

When you use SeeHub, our servers, and third party servers automatically record informations that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These servers' logs may include information such as the URL you visited, IP address, browser type and language, country, and the date and time of your request.

We are using third party services to record data: "Gostats.com", "Google Analytics", "Google adsense" and "Google Custom Search Engine"

We use this information to monitor the use of SeeHub (e.g. the numbers visitors). We only use this data for our statistics: Number of visits, new visits, impressions, page views, visits are up or down... This collective data helps us to improve SeeHub.

Cookies and beacons

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website to support it. These companies may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site and record information (not including your name, address, or telephone number but including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.   
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Our third-party advertising partner "Google" (throught "Adsense") use these cookies in combination with web beacons to serve ads and to analyze the effectiveness of the ads that they serve.

Google also use the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 

A cookie is a small text file containing a string of characters that a website sends your computer. It records information necessary for certain website functions, such as remembering your preferences or settings.

The cookie will not allow us or any third-party to learn any personally identifiable information that you have not otherwise disclosed.

Note: A web beacon is a small image file that is placed on a web page and used in conjunction with cookies to accurately count the number of unique users who have visited a specific page or viewed a specific advertisement. Any image file on a Web page can act as a Web beacon.

DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Changing SeeHub Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time.  
We will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.
